Topi Järvinen

topi.jarvinen1@gmail.com

+358 44 253 2790

Urjala, Finland





Bachelor of Business Administration, Information Technologies.

Junior Frontend / Game developer, also interested in Cybersecurity.

I have experience of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, React, Phaser and Unity.

I love creating new stuff and I am all about stylish visuals and colour worlds.

Education

Vaasa University Of Applied Sciences,

Bachelor of Business Administration, Information Technologies, 2020-2023, graduated

Projects

Homepage:

https://topi1.github.io/portfolio-site/

- HTML, CSS, JSX, React
- My responsive homepage. Includes links to other projects.

Horror game "Take My Hand?":

https://topi1.github.io/mystery-game/

- Currently working on this.
- This game is being created by using Phaser, HTML5 Game Framework. Languages in use are HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Webpack as bundler.
- Everything is done by me except the environment tilesets. All the other visual assets like the player character and UI assets are drawn by me with Aseprite.

Moonfang Build Guides:

https://topi1.github.io/moonfang/

- HTML, CSS, JSX, React
- My attempt on creating responsive, visually stylish website about video game builds and news.
- All the icons made by me in Canva. All the used images are usable since they are from press kits.
- This was my thesis project.

My GitHub profile: Topi1

<u>Skills</u>

Frontend Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript,

ReactJS

Backend Development: Basics of SQL and PHP

Game Development: C#, Unity, Phaser

Version Control: git, Plastic SCM
Operating Systems: Windows, Linux

Soft Skills: Good Teamworker, Adaptability, Problem-

Solving, Time Management

Languages: Finnish (native), English (good)

Work Experience

Platonic Partnership Oy (5/2022 – 9/2022)

Internship. Game development in a team. I did the programming on our game using Unity and C#.

Tays Hospital-Pharmacy (4/2020 – 8/2020)

Warehouse work.

Hoivakoti Reikonlinna (6/2019 – 8/2019)

Nursing.

References

Päivi Rajala

Doctor of Economics (IT), Principal Lecturer of Business Information Technology

Vaasa University Of Applied Sciences paivi.rajala@vamk.fi

Jussi Loukiainen

Chief Executive Officer

Platonic Partnership Oy jussi@platonicpartnership.com